[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "questionText": "Who is the main character of FFIX?",
    "answerList": [
      "Tidus",
      "Cloud Strife",
      "Zidane Tribal",
      "Squall Leonhart"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Zidane Tribal"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "questionText": "What's Garnet's temporary name to survive the world?",
    "answerList": [
      "Sera",
      "Yuffie",
      "Selphie",
      "Dagger"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Dagger"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "questionText": "What kind of mage is Vivi?",
    "answerList": [
      "Red",
      "White",
      "Black",
      "Blue"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Black"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "questionText": "What is the name of the enemy in FFIX?",
    "answerList": [
      "Ultimecia",
      "Kuja",
      "Sephiroth",
      "Jecht",
      "Gabranth"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Kuja"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "questionText": "What was the name of the bandits Zitane belonged?",
    "answerList": [
      "Tantalus",
      "Physalis",
      "Dontacos",
      "Banguilas"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Tantalus"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "questionText": "What is the name of the knights headed by Steiner?",
    "answerList": [
      "Goofy",
      "Pongo",
      "Max",
      "Pluto"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Pluto"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "questionText": "What is the name of Moogle, whose trademark is bandana and a big backpack, and who sell items everywhere to players?",
    "answerList": [
      "Mogunosuke",
      "Stiltzkin",
      "Kupo",
      "Artemicion"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Stiltzkin"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "questionText": "What is the letter delivery system between moogles?",
    "answerList": [
      "Mognet",
      "Mogmail",
      "Mog-SMS",
      "Mogservice"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Mognet"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "questionText": "Which summoned beast does not appear in FFIX?",
    "answerList": [
      "Shiva",
      "Leviathan",
      "Carbuncle",
      "Seiren"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Seiren"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "questionText": "What is the strongest weapon of a dagger equipped by Zidane?",
    "answerList": [
      "Orichalcon",
      "Assassin Dagger",
      "Chicken knife",
      "Gladius"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Orichalcon"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "questionText": "How many discs of PlayStation version software?",
    "answerList": [
      "One",
      "Two",
      "Three",
      "Four"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Four"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "questionText": "Whose equipment is Excalibur II, which is the strongest sword?",
    "answerList": [
      "Zidane Tribal",
      "Adelbert Steiner",
      "Freya Crescent",
      "Salamander Coral"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Adelbert Steiner"
  }
]